<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string
		name="app_name">Scripter</string>
	<string
		name="emailAddress">fazik.logic+scripter@gmail.com</string>
	<string
		name="dislaimerText">This program is provided as is without any guarantees or
		warranty.\nAlthough the author has attempted to find and correct any
		bugs in the free software programs, the author is not responsible for
		any damage or losses of any kind caused by the use or misuse of the
		program.\nThe author is under no obligation to provide support,
		service, corrections, or upgrades to the free software
		programs.\n\nThe purpose of this program is to change system files, by
		doing so bugs or errors can cause instability, total collapse or even
		rendering the device completely useless!\n\nUse it at your own risk!
	</string>
	<string
		name="about">\"Scripter\" was built to simplify the way users will run
		scripts.\nIf you have an idea, found a bug or want to make a
		suggestion then please use the \"Contact Developer\" option and send
		me an email.\n\nCredits:\nCode -\n* market-access\n* market-enabler\n*
		Su by ChainsDD\n* LouZiffer \nTesting -\n* Omer Itzhaki\n*
		nisim2337\n* Avraham Makovetsky\nBackgrounds -\n*
		www.patterncooler.com\n\n\"Scripter\" is a free open source project
		that was created by Dror Buhnik (Fazik Logic team of one)</string>
	<string
		name="guideString">\"Scripter\" is scripts application for android platform.\nThere
		are several ways you can run scripts while using this application:\n1)
		scan QR code that contains the commands\n2) run from every file
		explorer application by clicking on script file\n3) rerun any script
		that you already ran in the past\n4) manually create script and run
		it\n\n</string>
	<string
		name="changeLog">Version 1.8:\n* stdout and stderr info for each run (\'more
		info\' button after running script)\n* you can change background! see
		settings\n* you can now edit scripts\n* redesign of script list\n*
		framework for guide, will be in the next version\n* framework for
		running scripts without root permissions and running scripts after
		reboot, will be in the next version\n\nVersion 1.5:\n* Export/Import
		option to sdcard\n* Delete button foreach script\n* Create script
		manually from the application\n* Directing users without Busybox to
		the market application for easy installation\n* Better startup
		procedure\n* Bug fix</string>
	<string
		name="missingSu">Cannot find su binary in your device.\nIn order to use this
		application you must have root permissions.\n\nPlease head over to the
		web and search on methods to root your device.</string>
	<string
		name="missingBusybox">Cannot find Busybox binary in your device.\nIn order to use this
		application you must have busybox installed\n\nYou can search the
		market for "Busybox" application by Stericson that will install
		Busyboxy for you.\nOr install it yourself by searching the
		instructions in the web.</string>
	<string
		name="missingScanApp">Cannot find the scanning application.\nPlease install \"Barcode
		Scanner\" before using this option</string>
	<string
		name="noSdcard">Can\'t access sdcard. Make sure that he is inserted and
		accessible by the device</string>
	<string
		name="fileExists">Previous file already exists in your sdcard.\nDo you want to
		override it?</string>
</resources>